[Music]
Hey everyone, uh good evening and happy
Sabbath to you. Uh y'all go ahead and
put a one in the chat
uh to let me know that you see me, you
hear me.
And uh
just want to let you know that I am just
jumping on. This is just going to be a a
quick
a quick uh little video
um
that uh I'm doing just to talk about the
uh upcoming and that is Hey Renee, I see
you. Um that is Naomi. Welcome. Welcome.
Uh that is yes this is really live um
but I'm going to be talking about the
photo theology 7-day photo theology
course that is coming up and it actually
starts on Sunday.
Um
so for those of you who have been
following my ministry for any time um
any significant time you know that uh
photo theology is um a system that
uh I have used um and used it to put my
sermons together, put my Bible studies
together. It is the way that I study the
Bible and uh it is a very unique
approach to the scriptures
uh in which
uh for those of you again that that um
that have seen the system and understand
the system know that this system is not
a way of producing anything new. You do
not learn anything new in this system.
you're you're simply seeing old truths
from new perspectives, right? That is
the purpose of photo theology. Um, in
other words, think of it this way.
Truth can be seen from a thousand
different angles. And that's what
photoology is all about, right? It's
about learning how to see the Bible um
from a thousand different angles.
learning how to see the same truth from
multiple perspectives.
And so um
this uh photoology course understanding
photo theology in seven days is
basically a juiced down uh condensed
version of my longer photoology course.
Now
I have been teaching uh photo theology
um online for almost
somewhere I think it's four or five
years now and uh the class that I teach
online they have been with me many many
of them have been with me from the
beginning we're still going through
photo theology five years um uh into it
and we're still learning
so this 7-day class is really, you know,
a lot of people jump into that that
longer class and uh sometimes
they're like, "Man, I I I've missed so
much. Uh I kind of feel overwhelmed with
this because I've missed so much." Um
this 7-day course is going to be the
entire system juiced down into seven
days. So let me tell you a little bit
about the system. Um
so uh think of it in in terms of a
palace. Some of you may have heard me
explain this before. Think of the photo
theology system as a palace. In this
palace there are seven floors and on
each floor there are a series of rooms.
Each room represents a principle of
photo theology. And so altogether uh
there are 32
rooms in the photo theology palace. Each
one of these 32 rooms uh uh again
represents a principle but it's not just
one principle. So for example
uh on the third or on the fourth floor
of the photo theology palace there is
one room called the dimensions room.
And in the dimensions room there are
five different dimensions. There is the
literal dimension, there is the Christ
dimension, there is the me dimension,
there is the church dimension and there
is the heaven dimension.
So what that means is how do I read the
scriptures in each one of these
dimensions? And the easiest easiest
example uh that I like to use just to
give you a quick understanding is the
temple. In the Old Testament, God
instructed Moses to build a sanctuary
and inside that sanctuary was the very
presence of God. That is the first
dimension, right? The literal dimension.
The second dimension is basically asking
the question, where is Christ or how
does this relate to Christ? And we know
that in the New Testament Jesus says,
"Destroy this temple and I will raise it
again in three days." He was talking
about the temple of his body. So in the
second dimension, Christ is the temple
and the actual presence of God is
dwelling in him. Remember
that in the Old Testament, the temple
was in the center of the 12 tribes. So
Jesus is in the center of the 12
disciples. Right? This is the second
dimension. Christ is the temple. In the
third dimension,
um I am the temple. The Bible says,
"Know you not that you are the temple of
the Holy Ghost, right? And that the
spirit of God dwells in you."
So now we see three different
dimensions,
right? In other words, I can apply I
when I'm studying the sanctuary, I can
apply that sanctuary and all the aspects
of the sanctuary into those dimensions.
In the Old Testament, there was in the
Old Testament sanctuary, there was a
literal candlestick.
Christ is the light of the world. That's
the second dimension. Jesus says in
Matthew chapter 5, "Know you not that
you are the light of that uh uh you are
the light that a city set on a hill
cannot be hid, neither do men light uh a
candle and put it uh under a bushel, but
on a candlestick that it may give light
to all that are in the house." So you
can take each aspect of of the
sanctuary, the the table of showbread,
the altar of incense, the the seven
branch candlestick, the ark of the
covenant, and apply it in five different
dimensions. But we're keeping it simple.
We're keeping it simple for this just
for the sake of of understanding
the entire context of uh the the photo
theology palace. So the fourth dimension
would be the church dimension. All of us
together as lively stones make up the
house of God, the tabernacle of God, the
body of Christ.
And then there's a fifth dimension.
Hebrews chapter 8:9 tells us that there
is a heavenly sanctuary
in which Christ is dwelling. Now,
so what what you see here is that what
you begin to understand is whoa, most
people only read the Bible in two
dimensions. The literal dimension, what
does this verse literally mean? And then
this the third dimension, what does it
mean to me? Not even how is it how can I
see myself in the text, but just what
does it mean to me? So even in that
third dimension, they're not actually
taking it to the to the level of, oh, I
didn't know, you know, I didn't never
thought about I am the temple of the
Holy Ghost.
So
this room demonstrates then that you can
read the entire Bible in the first
dimension. What is the text literally
saying? And then read the entire Bible
in the second and then in the third and
then in the fourth and then in the
fifth. And if you only had this one
room, if you only learned this one room,
it would already amplify your study
beyond what you could imagine.
But you guys, this is only one room.
That's just one. There are 32
different rooms in the photo theology
system. And so what that means is that I
can take one verse and basically walk it
through each room. I might find
something powerful in the second
dimension on the in the dimension room
and then go to the to the fifth floor
and drop it in a room there and see
something else that just goes, "Oh,
wow." And then say, "Wait a minute. Let
me take this back to the dimensions room
and now apply the fourth dimension to
this. Oh man, that just opened up a
whole new discussion, a whole new train
of thought that I was not even thinking
before, that I've never even pursued
before.
Now you can begin to see the power of
this palace
and of this system.
Um,
many of you have heard me share this
story before, being in a mall with my
friends. I was about 18 years old at the
time and there they had just I guess
they had just come out with these
pictures
um and they're called magical eye
pictures. Magical eye pictures.
And the the the the
idea behind these pictures is when you
look at it,
all you see are a bunch of zigzag lines
that seem to have no p no pattern. know
it just looks like mess of an artwork of
artwork. It's just it just there's no
rhythm or rhyme to it. And I remember
seeing this picture for the first time
and going why is everybody so because
there was a group of people around and
they were like whoa whoa look at this
picture look oh my and I'm looking at
them like y'all are crazy. What are
y'all looking at? And someone says to me
you got to do this thing with your eyes.
You got to you got to cross your eyes.
you got to cross your eyes and I began
to cross my eyes. And I remember exactly
how I did it, but all of a sudden that
picture that looked like it made no
sense became like a 3D image. And when I
moved, the picture moved and now my mind
was blown. I was like, "What in the
world?" I was losing my mind.
Many of us when we come to the Bible and
we're reading stories in the Bible,
we're reading chapters in the Bible.
For many of us, it is like reading
zigzag lines. We are unable to see the
beauty that is laying beneath the
surface. We're unable to see the beauty
laying beneath the text.
However,
if we learn to cross our eyes,
I want you to catch what I'm saying, you
guys. If we learn to cross
our eyes,
in other words, if we learn that the
focus of scripture is Jesus and that we
should be looking for Jesus on every
page of the Bible, much like those Waldo
books that many of you remember as a
child,
trying to find Waldo on the page,
knowing he was there, not knowing he was
there, But not knowing exactly where he
was, the intrigue of those books was, I
got to find Waldo because I know he's
here. Jesus said, "Search the
scriptures, for in them you think you
have eternal life, and these are they
which testify of me." Meaning that
Jesus, beloved, is the very center and
focal point of all the Bible. That goes
for Leviticus, that goes for Genesis,
that goes for Numbers. Let me let me
just give you a quick Genesis.
When we say look for Jesus in the Bible,
most people are going to jump to
Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John, not
realizing
that
Jesus is the light of the world. Jesus
is the water of life. Jesus is the first
fruits that came out of the ground on
the third day. Jesus is the son of
righteousness. Jesus is the fisher of
men. Jesus is the man made in the image
of God. Jesus says, "Come unto me and I
will give you rest." In other words, in
those seven days of creation found in
Genesis chapter 1 and two, we find
shadows and symbols of Christ already.
Which means then that the Genesis
creation account is a snapshot of how
God recreates us in his image. Why?
Because before Christ comes into our
life, our life is without form
and void
and in darkness.
Photo theology is teaching you how to
see the Bible in pictures. You've heard
the term a picture is worth a thousand
words.
Well, this principle
of looking at the Bible and yes, the
words are important, but also
understanding that as we learn to
convert the words into images, as we
learn to convert the stories into
pictures, we begin to see matches, we
begin to see the scripture jump out at
us in a way that is just absolutely
mind-blowing.
Um,
and so this is what the class is about.
I'm going to give you one more example,
then I'm going to put the link up for
the class because the class begins
uh this Sunday, that is two days from
now. It is not going to be a huge class.
I want to keep the class small so that
the teacher student ratio is good, that
nobody gets lost in the mix.
Um,
but today you guys, I'm I'm not going to
tell you what book I was studying
because that's part of the surprise for
the sermon tomorrow. But last between
last night and today, I saw something
that just blew my mind. Part of it I
have seen before, which blew my mind.
But this other part of it, I was just
like, what in the world? And so I'm
preaching a sermon tomorrow entitled J a
letter to Judas.
and the third angel's message.
Now, you got to think that, huh? A
letter to Judas and the third a letter
in the Bible to Judas. Pastor, there's
no letter in the Bible to Judas.
But for those of you who tune in
tomorrow,
who are able to watch tomorrow, and even
if you can't watch that, if you've
watched my other sermons, if you watched
my blueprint presentation, if you've
watched my back to basics series, uh we
just finished a a Daniel in 7 days
course um uh last week in which our
students went on a journey through the
book of Daniel and saw things that they
have never seen before, but came out of
that class
more rooted and grounded
in our understanding of the book of
Daniel. Nothing new, nothing new, just
seeing it in a new perspective and a new
light.
How would you like to always open the
scriptures and see those zigzag lines
become 5D images?
How would you like to have that happen
every time you open the Bible? How would
you like to get a special pair of photo
theology glasses? And I'm speaking
symbolically here, but when you put
those photo theological glasses on,
those photo theology glasses on, you're
able to see the scripture in a light and
in a way that amplifies
the truth that we already have.
That is the goal of this photo theology
class. So, I'm going to put the link in
the chat and also I'm going to put it up
on the screen. So, for those of you who
still want to join the class, the class
I'm going to tell you this, the class is
already almost full. It's already almost
full. So, um, we have space for
I'm not going to say a few more people.
We have space for more people, but I
need to cut it off at a certain point.
So, um, we're going to put the link in
the the link is up on the screen,
myfototheology.com.
We will also put it in the link in the
chat. So, you can click on the link and
uh the class begins, as I said, Sunday.
It will go seven days beginning Sunday
evening, 700 p.m. Central Standard Time.
Um
after that class is done uh it'll be a
week a week break and then we're going
into our revelation for seven days. Um
we will then repeat. So my Daniel in
seven days course is coming back up
again. It will be I will be teaching it
again uh within the next six weeks. So
look out for that. If you miss this
Daniel course, you can take the next one
coming up. But uh that's it guys. Um,
we're going to close it out right here.
Um, again, the link is in the chat. It
is also uh on the on the screen for you
to to go to if you want to get into that
class. And I promise you um you will
come out of that class seeing the Bible
in an absolutely
powerful
new way. Nothing new,
but the same old truth of the three
angels messages simply amplified
a thousandx.
That's my promise to you. All right,
guys. That's it. May God bless you. Hope
to see you in the class and uh have a
happy upcoming Sabbath. And for those of
you that want to tune in tomorrow to
hear this message, a letter to Judas and
the third angel's message, don't miss
it, y'all. Living Mana online, uh 12:00
p.m. Central Standard Time after our
Sabbath school. Uh you're not going to
you're not going to want to miss it.
Again, may God bless you and uh have a
happy Sabbath.